ALYSSA WILLIAMS

alyssajanelwilliams@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/ajwilliams12/en https://github.com/alyssaw90

Profile

Upon graduating in 2012, I started my career in physical therapy. Working in physical therapy clinics I gained experience working with patients and health insurance. During this time I started thinking about how technology could change and improve the health care and health insurance industry. I started to teach myself how to code, and now I am in the General Assembly Web Development Immersive Course.

Skills

- Languages: JavaScript, Ruby, HTML, CSS
- Frameworks: Node.js, Express JS, Rails, AngularJS, Sailsjs
- Database Tools: SQL, PostgreSQL, Sequelize, ActiveRecord
- Authorization: Bcrypt
- Testing Frameworks: RSpec
- Other: Git/GitHub, Heroku, jQuery, AJAX, JSON, Bootstrap, Microsoft Office Suite

Experience

GENERAL ASSEMBLY, WEB DEVELOPMENT IMMERSIVE COURSE 2014- PRESENT

It is a 12 week intense and immersive course that teaches different languages and frameworks. During this course we are learning JavaScript, Express JS, Node.js, Ruby on Rails, AngularJS, and more. Also we 3 individual and group projects are completed during the course.

DIRECTOR OF REHAB ASSISTANT, INFINITY REHAB 2014

The facility was a large 140 bed facility where I worked directly with therapy, nursing, and office staff. My duties included completing the daily therapy schedule, keep compliance/HIPAA regulations up to date, keep DOR and therapy team organized, attend meetings, address patient, family and therapists concerns.

EXERCISE SPECIALIST, MARRAN PHYSICAL THERAPY 2013-2014

I worked directly with patients and the therapy team. My duties included starting patients, set up patient rooms, help patients with rehabilitation program, set patient up on different modalities, keep clinic organized/clean, help at front desk, and order supplies.

PHYSICAL THERAPY AIDE, PROLIANCE SPORTS THERAPY 2012-2013

I worked directly with patients and the therapy team. My duties included starting patients, set up patient rooms, help patients with rehabilitation program, set patient up on different modalities, keep clinic organized/clean, and, help at front desk.

Education

UNIVERSITY OF PORTLAND, PORTLAND, OREGON — LIFE SCIENCE B.S., 2012